A Guide to the Papers of Henry Heth, 1765-1800
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Letter from J. D. Williamson to John Heth 1819 Mar 4 (Box 12)
- Letter from A. M. Harrison to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 4 (Box 12)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Mr. Hughes 1819 Mar 9 (Box 12)
- Letter from A. M. Harrison to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 7 (Box 12)
- Letter from A. M. Harrison to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 8 (Box 12)
- Order of Chesterfield court exonerating Harry Heth as William Harris's security 1819 Mar 8 (Box 12)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 13 (Box 12)
- Letter from Samuel Pleasants to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 16 (Box 12)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 16 (Box 12)
- Letter from John Taliaferro to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 18 (Box 12)
- Letter from John B. Nicolson to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 18 (Box 12)
- Letter from Andrew Ramsay to Harry Heth 1819 23 (Box 12)
- Letter from William F. Carter to Beverly Randolph 1819 Apr 1 (Box 12)
- Letter from John Mason to Harry Heth 1819 Apr 5 (Box 12)
- Letter from Sam Christian to Harry Heth 1819 Apr 10 (Box 12)
- Letter from David Street to Harry Heth 1819 Apr 10 (Box 12)
- Letter from W. S. Stone to Harry Heth 1819 Apr 16 (Box 12)
- Letter from David Street to Harry Heth 1819 Apr 16 (Box 12)
- Letter from Andrew Ramsay to Harry Heth 1819 Apr 17 (Box 12)
- Letter from David Street to Harry Heth 1819 Apr 19 (Box 12)
- Letter from Elisha Cort to Harry Heth 1819 Apr 20 (Box 12)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Apr 21 (Box 12)
- Letter from John Taliaferro to [?] 1819 Apr 23 (Box 12)
- Letter from J. B. Dandridge to Harry Heth 1819 Apr 24 (Box 12)
- Letter from Thomas A. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Apr 27 (Box 12)
- Letter from W. S. Stone to Harry Heth 1819 May 3 (Box 12)
- Letter from Dan M. Railey to Harry 1819 May 4 (Box 12)
- Letter from W. Hampton to Harry Heth 1819 May 6 (Box 12)
- Letter from William M. Heth to Harry Heth 1819 May 9 (Box 12)
- Agreement between Harry Heth & Judith Nicolson 1819 May 10 (Box 12)
- Letter from A. M. Harrison to [?] 1819 May 13 (Box 12)
- Letter from W. S. Stone to Harry Heth 1819 May 14 (Box 12)
- Letter from Reuben Skelton to Harry Heth 1819 May 14 (Box 12)
- Letter from Thomas A. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 May 14 (Box 12)
- Letter from Thomas A. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 May 15 (Box 12)
- Letter from Thomas A. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 May 18 (Box 12)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Samuel Taylor & Ben Randolph 1819 May 24 (Box 12)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1819 May 18 (Box 12)
- Letter from John Osborne to [?] 1819 May 21 (Box 12)
- Letter from Ben Sheppard to Harry Heth 1819 May 22 (Box 12)
- Letter from John Davidson to Harry Heth 1819 May 23 (Box 12)
- Letter from Thomas A. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 May 23 (Box 12)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Dan McAtayton 1819 May 24 (Box 12)
- Letter from James Binford to Harry Heth 1819 May 24 (Box 12)
- Letter from J. Tidball to Harry Heth 1819 May 29 (Box 12)
- Letter from Ben Sheppard to Harry Heth 1819 May 25 (Box 12)
- Letter from G. Savage to Harry Heth 1819 May 26 (Box 12)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1819 May 28 (Box 12)
- Letter from Andrew Ramsay to Harry Heth 1819 May 29 (Box 12)
- Letter from Robert Pettigrew to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 1 (Box 12)
- Letter from J. Ganwood to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 1 (Box 12)
- Letter from Thomas Mann Randolph to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 2 (Box 12)
- Letter from William Browne to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 2 (Box 12)
- Letter from William Thompson, Jr., to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 8 (Box 12)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 8 (Box 12)
- Letter from Robert Pettigrew to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 9 (Box 12)
- Letter from George Beale, Jr., to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 9 (Box 12)
- Letter from Thomas White to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 10 (Box 12)
- Letter from Harry Heth to J. P. Pleasants 1819 Jun 12 (Box 12)
- Letter from Andrew Ramsey to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 13 (Box 12)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 15 (Box 12)
- Letter from W. A. Turpin to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 15 (Box 12)
- Letter from Thomas Mann Randolph to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 15 (Box 12)
- Letter from Dan M. Railey to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 15 (Box 12)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 19 (Box 12)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 20 (Box 12)
- Letter from J. Tidball to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 24 (Box 12)
- Letter from Randolph Harrison to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 25 (Box 12)
- Letter from Robert Pettigrew to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 25 (Box 12)
- Letter from A. B. Pillsborough to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 26 (Box 12)
- Letter from William Browne to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 28 (Box 12)
- Letter from John Browne to [?] 1819 Jun 28 (Box 12)
- Letter from Thomas Drew to Harry Heth 1819 Jun 30 (Box 12)
- Letter from George Beale to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 1 (Box 12)
- Letter from Robert Abbott, Jr., to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 1 (Box 12)
- Letter from William M. Heth to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 4 (Box 12)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 7 (Box 12)
- Letter from John Cundiffe to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 11 (Box 12)
- Letter from William Browne to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 12 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Randolph to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 17 (Box 13)
- Letter from Reuben Skelton to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 12 (Box 13)
- Letter from Richard Randolph to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 17 (Box 13)
- Letter from R. Tankersky to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 18 (Box 13)
- Letter from Elizabeth Railey to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 20 (Box 13)
- Letter from Otha Shipley to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 24 (Box 13)
- Letter from Reuben Skelton to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 25 (Box 13)
- Letter from R. Tankersky to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 26 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. W. Roysted to Harry Heth 1819 Jul 26 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Roddy to Harry Heth 1819 Aug 1 (Box 13)
- Letter from Osander Bishop to Harry Heth 1819 Aug 12 (Box 13)
- Letter from Robert Pettigrew to Harry Heth 1819 Aug 14 (Box 13)
- Letter from Robert Pettigrew to Harry Heth 1819 Aug 14 (Box 13)
- Letter from R. Tankersky to Harry Heth 1819 Aug 28 (Box 13)
- Letter from D. M. Randolph to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 23 (Box 13)
- Letter from Charles H. Braxton to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 30 (Box 13)
- Letter from J. Watkins & J. Wooldridge to Harry Heth 1819 Aug 31 (Box 13)
- Letter from A. M. Harrison to Harry Heth 1819 Sep 17 (Box 13)
- Letter from J. Tidball to Harry Heth 1819 Sep 7 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Sep 7 (Box 13)
- Letter from Ben Sheppard to Harry Heth 1819 Sep 9 (Box 13)
- Letter from Otha Shipley to Harry Heth 1819 Sep 10 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Sep 11 (Box 13)
- Letter from John E. Meade to Harry Heth 1819 Sep 18 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Heth to Harry Heth 1819 Sep 19 (Box 13)
- Letter from William Bently to Harry Heth 1819 Sep 27 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1819 Sep 27 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Tidball to Harry Heth 1819 Sep 30 (Box 13)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Warner Williams 1819 Oct 3 (Box 13)
- Letter from J. Gibbons to [?] 1819 Oct 4 (Box 13)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Henry Heth 1819 Oct 6 (Box 13)
- Letter from J. Tidball to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 5 (Box 13)
- Letter from James Brown, Jr., to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 7 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 8 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 9 (Box 13)
- Coal mines seminary 1819 Oct 10 (Box 13)
- Letter from E. Sully to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 11 (Box 13)
- Letter from Ben Sheppard to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 12 (Box 13)
- Letter from Thomas Lauther to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 12 (Box 13)
- Letter from Harry Heth to James Brown, Jr. 1819 Oct 12 (Box 13)
- Letter from W. S. Heath to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 16 (Box 13)
- Letter from John E. Meade to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 18 (Box 13)
- Letter from Thomas Lauther to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 20 (Box 13)
- Letter from H. Hackley to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 20 (Box 13)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 29 (Box 13)
- Letter from W. B. Pillsborough to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 30 (Box 13)
- Letter from W. Hampton to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 30 (Box 13)
- Letter from Richard Hughes to Harry Heth 1819 Oct 30 (Box 13)
- Letter from S. M. Harrison to Harry Heth 1819 Nov 1 (Box 13)
- Letter from C. L. Stevenson to Harry Heth 1819 Nov 5 (Box 13)
- Letter from D. M. Randolph to Harry Heth 1819 Nov 6 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Nov 6 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1819 Nov 7 (Box 13)
- Letter from James C. Anthony to [?] 1819 Nov 15 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1819 Nov 16 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Nov 19 (Box 13)
- Letter from D. M. Randolph to Harry Heth 1819 Nov 24 (Box 13)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1819 Nov 27 (Box 13)
- Letter from George Turner to Harry Heth 1819 Nov 29 (Box 13)
- Letter from J. Harrison to Harry Heth 1819 Nov 29 (Box 13)
- Harry Heth's will 1819 Dec 3 (Box 13)
- Letter from Wilson Allen to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 3 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Davidson to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 5 (Box 13)
- Letter from Algernon Sidney Mountain to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 5 (Box 13)
- Letter from Fontaine Maury to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 16 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Mason to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 11 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 12 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 14 (Box 13)
- Letter from Reuben Skelton to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 14 (Box 13)
- Letter from William Brown to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 15 (Box 13)
- Letter from Jean Wood to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 15 (Box 13)
- Letter from J. L. McKinna to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 17 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Ellicott to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 18 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 18 (Box 13)
- Letter from Andrew Ramsey to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 19 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 20 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 22 (Box 13)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 23 (Box 13)
- Letter from R. B. Maury to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 23 (Box 13)
- Letter from A. B. Allen to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 20 (Box 13)
- Letter from Archibald Freedman to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 29 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Dec 30 (Box 13)
- Articles of agreement between Robert Wren & Harry Heth 1819 (Box 13)
- Accounts and receipts for 1819 1819 (Box 13)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 181[?] Mar 17 (Box 13)
- Letter from S. Davidson to Beverly Randolph 181[?] Nov 9 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Heth to Harry Heth 181[?] (Box 13)
- Letter from John Randolph to Harry Heth 181[?] (Box 13)
- Letter from F. B. Ogden to [?] 181[?] (Box 13)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 181[?] (Box 13)
- Letter from C. & R. Railey to Harry Heth 181[?] (Box 13)
- Letter from B. Randolph to James Vass 181[?] (Box 13)
- George Hay's opinion on Heth case 181[?] (Box 13)
- Letter from B. Randolph to [?] 181[?] (Box 13)
- Letter from D. M. Randolph to Harry Heth 181[?] (Box 13)
- Letter from [?] to [?] 181[?] (Box 13)
- Extract from deed - Cary to Cox for Cundiffe 181[?] (Box 13)
- Letter from D. Meade to Harry Heth 181[?] (Box 13)
- List of Negroes 181[?] (Box 13)
- Accounts and receipts 181[?] (Box 13)
- Agreement between Harry Heth & A. M. Harrison [1820] (Box 13)
- Letter from J. Mosby to Harry Heth 1820 Jan (Box 13)
- Letter from J. C. Anthony to Harry Heth 1820 Jan 1 (Box 13)
- Letter from John E. Meade to Harry Heth 1820 Jan 2 (Box 13)
- Letter from George Savage to Harry Heth 1820 Jan 3 (Box 13)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1820 Jan 3 (Box 13)
- Letter from David M. Forrest to Harry Heth 1820 Jan 3 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1820 Jan 10 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1820 Jan 12 (Box 13)
- Letter from C. Rogers to Harry Heth 1820 Jan 20 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1820 Jan 22 (Box 13)
- Letter from J. Kirkpatrick to Harry Heth 1820 Jan 29 (Box 13)
- Letter from James Davis to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 7 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Randolph to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 18 (Box 13)
- Letter from C. B. Page to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 1 (Box 13)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 2 (Box 13)
- Letter from C. & R. Railey to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 2 (Box 13)
- Letter from J. Nelson to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 3 (Box 13)
- Letter from Harry Heth to R. Wren 1820 Feb 5 (Box 13)
- Letter from D. W. Mitchell to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 7 (Box 13)
- Letter from B. Randolph to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 9 (Box 13)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 10 (Box 13)
- Affidavit of John E. Meade 1820 Feb 10 (Box 13)
- Letter from R. Abbott to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 11 (Box 13)
- Letter from Archibald Freeland to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 11 (Box 13)
- Letter from A. Robinson to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 12 (Box 13)
- Letter from Samuel Taylor to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 13 (Box 13)
- Letter from R. Abbott to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 14 (Box 13)
- Letter from Robert Taylor to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 15 (Box 13)
- Letter from W. C. & G. Clark to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 16 (Box 13)
- Letter from D. Robinson to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 16 (Box 13)
- Letter from B. Randolph to [?] 1820 Feb 17 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Watson to John Landy 1820 Feb 17 (Box 14)
- Letter from B. Tate to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 17 (Box 14)
- Letter from W. C. & G. Clark to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 17 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 18 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 18 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 19 (Box 14)
- Letter from Samuel Taylor to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 20 (Box 14)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 23 (Box 14)
- Letter from J. Mason to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 24 (Box 14)
- Letter from Henry E. Watkins to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 25 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 26 (Box 14)
- Letter from Alfred Hughes to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 27 (Box 14)
- Letter from Richard Randolph to Harry Heth 1820 Feb 27 (Box 14)
- Letter from B. Randolph to [?] 1820 Feb 29 (Box 14)
- Letter from B. Randolph to [?] 1820 Mar 2 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1820 Mar 3 (Box 14)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1820 Mar 3 (Box 14)
- Letter from Archibald Freeland to Harry Heth 1820 Mar 3 (Box 14)
- Letter from Robert Christian to Harry Heth 1820 Mar 4 (Box 14)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Harry Heth 1820 Mar 14 (Box 14)
- Letter from F. S. Taylor to Harry Heth 1820 Mar 20 (Box 14)
- Letter from John J. Wirth to Harry Heth 1820 Mar 30 (Box 14)
- Letter from [?] to Harry Heth 1820 Apr 24 (Box 14)
- Letter from Harry Heth to R. Wren 1820 May 1 (Box 14)
- Letter from Robert Taylor to Harry Heth 1820 Jun 6 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Heth to Harry Heth 1820 Jun 20 (Box 14)
- Letter from Harry Heth to John Heth 1820 Jul 17 (Box 14)
- Letter from Caleb Heath to Harry Heth 1820 Jul 19 (Box 14)
- Letter from J. A. Chevallie to PascalLesseps 1820 Jul 21 (Box 14)
- Letter from Richard Hughes to Harry Heth 1820 Jul 22 (Box 14)
- Letter from H. G. Heth to Harry Heth 1820 Sep 20 (Box 14)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Henry Heth 1820 Sep 29 (Box 14)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1820 Dec 9 (Box 14)
- Letter from James Force to Harry Heth 1820 Dec 24 (Box 14)
- Letter from Virginia Heth & R. Harrison to Harry Heth 1820 Dec 27 (Box 14)
- Letter from Algernon Sidney Mountain to Harry Heth 1820 Dec 27 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Heth to Harry Heth 1820 Dec 28 (Box 14)
- Accounts and receipts for 1820 1820 (Box 14)
- Letter from Isaac Read & Co., to Harry Heth 1821 Jan 11 (Box 14)
- Letter from M. Burfoot to Lawson Burfoot 1821 Jan 23 (Box 14)
- Letter from E. T. Heth to Harry Heth 1821 Jan 23 (Box 14)
- Will of Harry Heth 1821 Jan 23 (Box 14)
- Letter from James Sheppard to John Heth 1821 Jan 27 (Box 14)
- Letter from Henry B. Christian to Henry Heth 1827 Mar (Box 14)
- Letter from C. Outts to Henry Heth 1821 Mar 9 (Box 14)
- Letter from Richard O. Henderson to Henry Heth 1821 Mar 26 (Box 14)
- Letter from B. Tom & Co. to Henry Heth 1821 Mar 28 (Box 14)
- Letter from B. Tom & Co. to Henry Heth 1821 Mar 29 (Box 14)
- Letter from Richard Hughes to Henry Heth 1821 Apr 3 (Box 14)
- Letter from Isaac Read to Harry Heth 1821 Apr 4 (Box 14)
- Letter from Richard Hughes to Henry Heth 1821 Apr 10 (Box 14)
- Letter from James Harris to Henry Heth 1821 Apr 12 (Box 14)
- Letter from Isaac Read to Harry Heth 1821 Apr 26 (Box 14)
- Letter from Lambert & Keith to Henry Heth 1821 May 5 (Box 14)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Henry Heth 1821 May 17 (Box 14)
- Haley Cole's certificate of apprehending runaway slave 1821 Jun 7 (Box 14)
- Letter from Harry Heth to James Organ 1821 Jun 22 (Box 14)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Robert Garnett 1821 Jul 12 (Box 14)
- Letter from Richard Waltham to Henry Heth 1821 Jul 20 (Box 14)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Henry Heth 1821 Jul 21 (Box 14)
- Letter from J. Crump to Henry Heth 1821 Aug 9 (Box 14)
- Letter from Samuel Taylor to Harry Heth 1821 Aug 15 (Box 14)
- Letter from H. Heth to J. H. Cundiffe 1821 Nov 28 (Box 14)
- Letter from J. West to Henry Heth 1821 Dec 7 (Box 14)
- Accounts and receipts for 1821 1821 (Box 14)
- Letter from J. Read & Co. to Harry Heth 1822 Jan 7 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Randolph to Henry Heth 1822 Jan 15 (Box 14)
- Letter from Meridith Hilliard to Harry Heth 1822 Mar 10 (Box 14)
- Note-E. W. Poindexter 1822 Mar 11 (Box 14)
- Letter from R. Randolph to Henry Heth 1822 Mar 12 (Box 14)
- Letter from J. Read & Co. to Harry Heth 1822 Mar 17 (Box 14)
- Accounts and receipts for 1822 1822 (Box 14)
- Statement of John Heth 1823 May 12 (Box 14)
- Letter from H. Heth to John Heth 1823 May 12 (Box 14)
- Accounts and receipts for 1823 1823 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Heth to W. Ritcher 1824 Sep 22 (Box 14)
- Accounts and receipts for 1824 1824 (Box 14)
- Accounts and receipts for 1825 1825 (Box 14)
- Letter from W. Woolsey to Commodore Hull 1825 (Box 14)
- Accounts and receipts for 1826-1827 1826-1827 (Box 14)
- Letter from T. B. Dudley to John Heth 1827 Mar 30 (Box 14)
- Letter from Thomas Miller to Harry Heth 1827 Apr 22 (Box 14)
- Trust bond-Heth to Pickett 1827 Jun 12 (Box 14)
- Accounts and receipts for 1827 1827 (Box 14)
- Letter from W. Woolsey to Samuel L. Linhard 1828 Jan 15 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Heth to Beverly Randolph 1825 Jul 24 (Box 14)
- Accounts and receipts for 1828 1828 (Box 14)
- Letter from H. Meade to John Heth 1829 Jan 5 (Box 14)
- Letter from S. Nunnally to B. Randolph 1829 (Box 14)
- Letter from John Heth to R. F. Stockton 1829 May 11 (Box 14)
- Accounts and receipts for 1829 Jan-Jun 1829 (Box 15)
- Letter from W. Mercer to Beverly Randolph 1829 Oct 29 (Box 15)
- Receipt for cargo brig Caroline 1829 Dec 22 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1829 Jul-Dec 1829 (Box 15)
- Memorandum of agreement between B. Randolph, John Heth, & G. B. Wooldridge 1830 Jan 10 (Box 15)
- Letter from M. Mercer to Beverly Randolph 1830 Apr 12 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1830 Jan-Jun 1830 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1830 Jul-Dec 1830 (Box 15)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Charles A. Randolph 1831 Feb 2 (Box 15)
- Pedigree for convention 1831 Feb 5 (Box 15)
- Memorandum of agreement between B. Randolph, John Heth, & David Hancock 1831 Feb 10 (Box 15)
- Appointment of John Heth as captain in the militia 1831 Apr 14 (Box 15)
- Letter from M. Mercer to Beverly Randolph 1831 May 4 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1831 Jan-Jun 1831 (Box 15)
- Letter from M. Mercer to Beverly Randolph 1831 Oct 4 (Box 15)
- Letter from E. H. Randolph to Beverley Randolph 1831 Nov 19 (Box 15)
- Letter from A. H. Harrison to B. Randolph 1831 Dec 14 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1831 Jul-Dec 1831 (Box 15)
- Letter from Thomas J. C. Monroe to John Heth 1832 Feb 10 (Box 15)
- Letter from Charles Cundiffe to Mssrs. Harding & Watkins 1832 Apr 28 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1832 Jan-Jun 1832 (Box 15)
- Letter from [?] to Nancy Randolph 1832 Sep 23 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1832 Jul-Oct 1832 (Box 15)
- Letter from W. B. Caldwell to John Heth 1832 Nov 6 (Box 15)
- Deed-W. J. Cary estate to Archibald M. Harrison 1832 Nov 7 (Box 15)
- Copy of trust deed-Harrison to Strange & Timberlake 1832 Nov 7 (Box 15)
- Trust deed-Harrison to John Heth & Beverly Heth 1832 Nov 7 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1832 Nov-Dec 1832 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1833 Jan-Jun 1833 (Box 15)
- Charles H. Randolph's diploma from the University of Virginia 1833 Jul 18 (Box 15)
- Letter from Thomas R. Harrison to John Heth 1833 Jul 23 (Box 15)
- Letter from George W. Banks to John Heth 1833 Jul 24 (Box 15)
- Letter from William F. Kennon to Edmond Fitzgerald 1833 Nov 28 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1833 Jul-Dec 1833 (Box 15)
- Letter from John Heth to L. M. Tazewell 1834 Sep 24 (Box 15)
- Deed-Richard Roberts and others to Abram S. Wooldridge 1834 Mar 19 (Box 15)
- Letter from W. F. Ritchie to William S. Archer 1834 Sep 24 (Box 15)
- Letter from David C. Randolph to John Heth 1834 (Box 15)
- Letter from William S. Archer to William Ritchie 1834 Sep 24 (Box 15)
- Letter from John Baker to John Heth 1834 Oct 31 (Box 15)
- Letter from I. Martin to John Heth 1834 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1834 1834 (Box 15)
- John Heth's commission as captain 1835 Mar 10 (Box 15)
- Letter from John N. Lloyd to John W. Watson 1835 Apr 15 (Box 15)
- Letter from Secretary of War to John Heth 1835 Apr 25 (Box 15)
- Letter from H. Meade to John Heth 1835 Jun 2 (Box 15)
- Letter from A. C. Gwathmey to Charles H. Randolph 1835 Jul 9 (Box 15)
- Memorandum of travels in Europe 1835 Aug 12-14 (Box 15)
- Letter from Thomas L. Pleasants to [?] 1835 Aug 25 (Box 15)
- Accounts and receipts for 1835 1835 (Box 15)
- Letter from [?] to Charles Randolph 1836 Mar (Box 15)
- Letter from H. Lee to Charles Randolph 1836 Mar 21 (Box 15)
- Letter from G. J. Thornton to Charles Randolph 1836 Jun 6 (Box 15)
- Letter from N. Kennon to Charles Randolph 1836 Jun 14 (Box 15)
- Letter from R. A. Swann to John Heth 1836 Jun 14 (Box 15)
- Statement of Richard A. Swann 1836 Jun 17 (Box 15)
- Letter from [?] to Charles Randolph 1836 Dec 7 (Box 16)
- Accounts and receipts for 1836 Jan-Sep 1836 (Box 16)
- Letter from W. Hampton to John Heth 1830 Oct 8 (Box 16)
- Letter from W. Hampton to John Heth 1836 Oct 12 (Box 16)
- Letter from J. S. Skinner to John Heth 1836 Oct 15 (Box 16)
- Letter from J. S. Skinner to John Heth 1836 Oct 31 (Box 16)
- Letter from Benjamin Ogle Tayloe to [?] 1836 Nov 5 (Box 16)
- Letter from Isidore Guillet to C. Randolph 1836 Nov 19 (Box 16)
- Letter from G. C. Powell to John Heth 1836 Nov 23 (Box 16)
- Letter from George H. Lee to C. Randolph 1836 Nov (Box 16)
- Letter from George H. Lee to C. Randolph 1836 Nov (Box 16)
- Letter from Z. Williams to John Heth 1836 Dec 4 (Box 16)
- Letter from A. Foster & Long to John Heth 1836 Dec 5 (Box 16)
- Letter from J. McClellan to John Heth 1836 Dec 14 (Box 16)
- Letter from J. B. Beverly to J. S. Skinner 1836 Dec 17 (Box 16)
- Letter from Thomas S. Pleasants to William Scott 1836 Dec 20 (Box 16)
- Letter from Lewis Rogers & Co. to Charles Randolph 1836 Dec 28 (Box 16)
- Letter from James Lyons to John Heth 1836 Dec 30 (Box 16)
- Letter from Neill to Thomas Randolph 1836 (Box 16)
- Letter from George H. Lee to Charles Randolph 1836 (Box 16)
- Accounts and receipts for 1836 Oct-Dec 1836 (Box 16)
- Notes on medical subjects 1836 (Box 16)
- Letter from Beverly Kennon to William H. Gardner 1837 Feb 5 (Box 16)
- Letter from Lewis Rogers & Co. to Charles Randolph 1837 Sep 6 (Box 16)
- Letter from S. Warrington to Arthur Lewis 1837 Oct 17 (Box 16)
- Letter from C. O'Donnell to John Heth 1837 Dec 16 (Box 16)
- Letter from W. Seldon to John Heth 1837 Dec 22 (Box 16)
- Letter from E. N. Childe to C. Randolph 1837 (Box 16)
- Letter from [?] to John Heth 1837 (Box 16)
- Report of subjects studied by Charles Randolph 1837 (Box 16)